{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Information Assurance & Security (Cybersecurity Fundamentals)",
    "Term": "Prelims",
    "Title": "02 Handout 1 -- ALL TOPICS",
    "LastModified": "19 February 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "02 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData":  [
    {
      "question": "Employees can create some of the greatest risks to cybersecurity.",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Processes",
        "Technology",
        "Security Audits",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "When they are well informed, however, they can also be an asset and the first line of defense.",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Processes",
        "Technology",
        "Security Policies",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Often, cybercriminals will specifically target employees as an attack vector based on their lack of knowledge for security practices.",
      "answer": "People",
      "choices": [
        "Processes",
        "Technology",
        "Security Audits",
        "People"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This layer of cybersecurity ensures that IT teams have strategies in place to proactively prevent and to respond quickly and effectively in the event of a cybersecurity incident.",
      "answer": "Processes",
      "choices": [
        "People",
        "Technology",
        "Security Policies",
        "Processes"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "IT security teams should have a cyber-incident response plan in place.",
      "answer": "Processes",
      "choices": [
        "People",
        "Technology",
        "Security Policies",
        "Processes"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "There are hosts of these that security teams can implement to layer their defenses.",
      "answer": "Technology",
      "choices": [
        "People",
        "Processes",
        "Security Audits",
        "Technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This can be especially important when it comes to the Internet of Things (IoT) where the network of connected devices ensures that any device that seeks to be connected has the rights for connectivity to that particular network.",
      "answer": "Hardware authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Cloud technology",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Hardware authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a well-known fact that a majority of data usersâ€™ passwords and usernames are weak and makes it easy for hackers to get access to the information systems and compromise sensitive data of a business entity or government agency.",
      "answer": "Hardware authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Cloud technology",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Hardware authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is set to have a significant impact on the transformation of systems security technology.",
      "answer": "Cloud technology",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Cloud technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "More business enterprises and government agencies have embraced cloud technology to store the vast amounts of information that they generate daily.",
      "answer": "Cloud technology",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Deep learning",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Cloud technology"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This encompasses some technologies like machine learning and artificial intelligence.",
      "answer": "Deep learning",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Cloud technology",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Deep learning"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "There is a significant deal of interest for systems security in these technologies.",
      "answer": "Deep learning",
      "choices": [
        "Hardware Authentication",
        "Cloud technology",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Deep learning"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many types of Cybersecurity (Security rendered in the network) mentioned in the handout?",
      "answer": "Five",
      "choices": [
        "Two",
        "Three",
        "Four",
        "Five"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This consists of the cyber-physical systems that modern societies rely on.",
      "answer": "Critical Infrastructure Security",
      "choices": [
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is more accessible over networks, causing the adoption of security measures during the development phase to be an imperative phase of the project.",
      "answer": "Application Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Application Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This ensures that internal networks are secured by protecting the infrastructure and inhibiting access to it.",
      "answer": "Network Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Network Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a software-based security tool that protects and monitors data in cloud resources.",
      "answer": "Cloud Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cloud providers are constantly creating and implementing new security tools to help enterprise users better secure their data.",
      "answer": "Cloud Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "This refers to a wide variety of critical and non-critical cyber-physical systems like appliances, sensors, televisions, Wi-Fi routers, printers, and security cameras.",
      "answer": "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
      "choices": [
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Electricity grid, water purification traffic lights, shopping centers, and hospitals.",
      "answer": "Critical Infrastructure Security",
      "choices": [
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Antivirus programs, firewalls, and encryption.",
      "answer": "Application Security",
      "choices": [
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
        "Cloud Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Application Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Extra logins, new passwords, and application security (firewalls, monitored Internet access, antispyware, antivirus)",
      "answer": "Network Security",
      "choices": [
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Network Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Software as a Service, Infrastructure as a Service, private, on-site cloud, and virtualization.",
      "answer": "Cloud Security",
      "choices": [
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Critical Infrastructure Security",
        "Cloud Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Connected security systems, thermostats, cars, electronic appliances, and speaker systems.",
      "answer": "Internet of Things (IoT) Security",
      "choices": [
        "Cloud Security",
        "Network Security",
        "Application Security",
        "Internet of Things (IoT) Security"
      ],
      "reference": "Subjects and Objects of Security",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a set of rules that applies to activities for the computer and communications resources that belong to an organization?",
      "answer": "Security Policy",
      "choices": [
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Security Policy"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should describe how the effectiveness of security measures will be monitored?",
      "answer": "Security Policy",
      "choices": [
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Security Policy"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What ensures that only authorized users can access objects on the system?",
      "answer": "Resource Protection",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Resource Protection"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the ability to secure all types of system resources refer to?",
      "answer": "Resource Protection",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization",
        "Resource Protection"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance or verification that the resource (human or machine) at the other end of the session really is what it claims to be?",
      "answer": "Authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authorization",
        "Authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which security objective does digital certificates provide a more secure method refers to?",
      "answer": "Authentication",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authorization",
        "Authentication"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an assurance that the person or computer at the other end of the session has permission to carry out the request?",
      "answer": "Authorization",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is performed in context application?",
      "answer": "Authorization",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Authorization"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance that the arriving information is the same as what was sent out?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does understanding integrity require?",
      "answer": "Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is protected from unauthorized changes or tampering?",
      "answer": "Data Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Data Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does data integrity defend against?",
      "answer": "Data Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Data Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What provides consistent and expected results with expected performance?",
      "answer": "System Integrity",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "System Integrity"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the proof that a transaction occurred, or that a user sent or received a message?",
      "answer": "Nonrepudiation",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Nonrepudiation"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the assurance that sensitive information remains private and is not visible to an eavesdropper?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is critical to total data security?",
      "answer": "Confidentiality",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What monitors security-relevant events to provide a log of both successful and unsuccessful (denied) access?",
      "answer": "Auditing Security Activities",
      "choices": [
        "Security Policy",
        "Resource Protection",
        "Authentication",
        "Auditing Security Activities"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What records tell who is doing what on the systems?",
      "answer": "Successful access",
      "choices": [
        "Unsuccessful access",
        "Graduating access",
        "Access Point",
        "Successful access"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What records tell either that someone is attempting to break the security or that someone is having difficulty accessing the system?",
      "answer": "Unsuccessful access",
      "choices": [
        "Unsuccessful access",
        "Graduating access",
        "Access Point",
        "Successful access"
      ],
      "reference": "Security Objectives",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a federal agency within the United States Department of Commerce?",
      "answer": "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
      "choices": [
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's mission is to develop and promote measurement, standards, and technology to enhance productivity, facilitate trade, and improve the quality of life and also establishes IT standards and guidelines for federal agencies?",
      "answer": "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
      "choices": [
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was developed by the International Organization for Standardization?",
      "answer": "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can any type or size of organization benefit from?",
      "answer": "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "Security architecture",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a systematic approach to managing sensitive information securely?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes managing risk for people, processes, and IT systems?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is divided into different sub-standards?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes a six-part approach?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is also known as the Information Security Management System [ISMS]?",
      "answer": "ISO 27000",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
        "ISO 27000"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was initiated to ensure businesses process card payments were secure and to help reduce card fraud?",
      "answer": "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS)"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a unified security design that addresses the necessities and potential risks involved in a particular scenario or environment?",
      "answer": "Security architecture",
      "choices": [
        "National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)",
        "ISO/IEC 27000 family",
        "ISO 27000",
        "Security architecture"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What signifies the relationship between the various components inside IT architecture and how they depend on each other?",
      "answer": "Relationships and Dependencies",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is security architecture's main advantage?",
      "answer": "Standardization",
      "choices": [
        "Standardization",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Benefits"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is cost-effective due to the re-use of controls described in the architecture?",
      "answer": "Benefits",
      "choices": [
        "Standardization",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Benefits"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is associated with IT architecture?",
      "answer": "Form",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What includes a catalog of conventional controls in addition to relationship diagrams and principles?",
      "answer": "Form",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are security controls determined based on?",
      "answer": "Drivers",
      "choices": [
        "Benefits",
        "Form",
        "Drivers",
        "Relationships and Dependencies"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What evaluates the business influence of vital business assets and the odds and effects of vulnerabilities and security threats?",
      "answer": "Architecture Risk Assessment",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the design and architecture of security services, which facilitate business risk exposure objectives?",
      "answer": "Security Architecture and Design",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are security services and processes implemented, operated and controlled?",
      "answer": "Implementation",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the day by day processes, such as threat and vulnerability management and threat management?",
      "answer": "Operations and Monitoring",
      "choices": [
        "Security Architecture and Design",
        "Implementation",
        "Operations and Monitoring",
        "Architecture Risk Assessment"
      ],
      "reference": "IT Security Framework and Security Architecture",
      "term": "Prelims"
    }
  ]
}